Leandro Loiácono



web developer experience (Projects)

Project 'Travelwith'

Web-app for organize travel with friends.

Project 'localSHOP://

Web for local small business (JS, SCSS, MongoDB)

Project 'did you watch this?'

Project of a web for movie recommendations (JS)

experience

Teacher Assistant

IRONHACK Sept 2020 - Dec 2020

Teacher Assistant for the WebDev. Bootcamp.

Content Moderator

Majorel May 2019 - Jun 2020

Content analysis and moderation for one of the biggest social media companies worldwide.

Customer service Supervisor

Hospital Aleman Services Apr 2012 - Dec 2018

Coordinate and train a team of agents of customer services for a health care insurance company.

education

Full Stack Developer Bootcamp

Ironhack Jun 2020 - Sept 2020

Professional Photographer

Escuela Fotografía Andy Goldstein Feb 2017 - Nov 2018

contact

leandro.a.loiacono@gmail.com

Tel: +34 693 004488

LinkedIn: @leandro-loiacono/

Github: @leanloia

bio

My professional path started in Argentina, where I worked in the Customer Services Industry for some years and, in parallel, dedicate my free time to get more involved in other areas, such as Programming, Photography and learning new languages.

In the beginning of 2019, I decided to move to Barcelona, and change my professional and personal life almost completely. I decided to make a career change and I joined a Full Stack WebDev Bootcamp at Ironhack, and currently I'm starting a new path in a new Industry, which fills me with excitement and push me forward to a new self-development path.

skills & expertise

- JavaScript
- React.js
- MongoDB
- Node.js
- Express.js
- HTML & CSS
- Spanish (native)
- English (advanced)
- Catalan (intermediate)
- German (begginer)